VLADYSLAV SHEIKO

Senior Software Engineer

Plovdiv, Bulgaria



SUMMARY

Specializing in back-end, front-end, and database development with technologies such as .NET, React, Angular, and MSSQL, I bring extensive experience across CXM, consulting, IoT, and human resources domains. I have thrived in both large teams (over 30 members) and smaller agile groups (5-10 members).

TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE OVERVIEW

.NET - 7 years SQL Server - 7 years Angular - 2.5 years React - 2 years

TECHNOLOGIES

C#, ASP.NET, .NET Core, EF, Dapper HTML/CSS, JS, TS, React, Angular 2+ MSSQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, RabbitMQ, Linux, Bash, Git, PowerShell, Jenkins, Docker, Python, TeamCity, Octopus Deploy, Azure DevOps SDLC, Agile, Scrum

SOFT SKILLS

Flexibility

Precision and thoroughness

Task prioritization

Issue resolution

Teamwork

Communication

VOLUNTEERING

Volunteering together for Human Rights

European Solidarity Corps

= 02/2024 - 04/2024

• Improved career opportunities for 20 refugees by providing tailored software engineering learning guidance.

LANGUAGES

Native | | | | Ukrainian English Proficient | | | | German Beginner | | | | |

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer (.NET)

Domain: Customer Experience Management (CXM)

- Played a key role in the development of a comprehensive CXM solution, enabling companies in the automotive, banking, insurance, and power industries to track and analyze customer feedback.
- · Engineered an innovative CX survey suggestion system, optimizing customer feedback collection and empowering companies to improve their
- · Led a team of 2 .NET developers, fostering a collaborative environment that drove efficient project execution and continuous improvement.
- · Spearheaded the design of various API modules, enhancing overall application integration and performance.
- · Collected requirements and conduct estimates for clients.

Middle Software Engineer (.NET, Angular)

Infopulse

= 02/2021 - 05/2023

Kyiv, Ukraine, Remote

Domain: Consulting

- Participated in solution development for one of big four accounting firms.
- Design, develop and deliver new features on time and within budget.
- Refactored legacy code, based on .NET Core 2.0.
- · Writing of comprehensive unit tests using xUnit and MOQ.
- · Performed code and design reviews.
- · Investigated for new features and functionalities and document requirements in Azure DevOps.
- · Participated in estimation and planning sessions.

Strong Junior Software Engineer (.NET, React)

Odessa Innovative Technology lab

= 01/2019 - 02/2021

Odesa, Ukraine

Domain: IoT

- Developed and integrated web-based applications using .NET Core 3.1, Entity Framework, and React.
- Designed and implemented optimization in a database structure in SQL Server.
- · Configured continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) pipelines in TeamCity and Octopus Deploy.
- Set up a VMware virtualization environment for testing and development.
- · Developed reusable and maintainable code by adhering to SOLID principles and best
- Optimized database queries and implemented database migrations on SQL Server.

Junior Software Engineer (.NET)

KeepSolid Inc

= 06/2018 - 01/2019

Odesa, Ukraine

Domain: Human Resources

- Improved product quality by reducing stabilization bugs to zero in 2 critical features
- Designed and implemented optimization in a database structure in MySQL.
- Found and fixed critical bugs during covering legacy code with unit tests.
- · Unit testing of main business functionality.

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Software Engineering

Odessa National Telecommunications Academy

= 09/2021 - 01/2023